FROM ME TO YOU
Back when I was in elementary school, I
wasn't necessarily disliked by anyone.
But I never made any close friends, or
was part of any social circles either.
Can I join, you guys?
- Didn't see you there, Sawako.
- Yeah sure, you can play with us.
Shino, a classmate of
mine, called out to me one day.
- Hey, Sadako!
- Her misspeaking my name was the start.
Sadako?
- Sadako, huh?
- It's Sadako!
I've been known as "Sadako" since. In
middle school, some of my classmates
started a joke about me...
- Sadako looks like she has a sixth sense!
- I wouldn't be surprised if that was true.
It is true, it's gotta be!
Before I knew it, I was tied to the
occult. Things weren't much different once
I entered high school...
- I hear Sadako can talk to the dead.
- Also, if your eyes meet for over
three-seconds, then in seven days...
And from there, the rumors all
began to snowball... supposedly.
That being said, when I look back at
everything, I actually think I was pretty
fortunate up to this point. While I did
get upset at times, I can't recall ever
feeling like I was truly miserable.
I've been meaning to mention...
You remember that Sadako rumor?
The one about Yano and
Yoshida being her backup?
It's a misunderstanding!
Those two girls aren't my backup. Nor
have they ever been anything like that.
Shut the hell up. We get it.
But... it's totally true that
they're a slut and a delinquent, right?
Morning, Kazehaya.
Morning.
- Morning, Ryu.
- Same to you. Huh?
Uh...
- That's a huge crowd.
- What happened?
- Oh, hey there, Kazehaya.
- There's an argument
- in the girls bathroom.
- There is?
You're never gonna guess
who's involved in it though!
It's Sadako and some girls from Class A!
- Kuronuma?! But why?
- We were in there with
them and heard everything...
Those rumors spreading about Yano and
Yoshida... I guess Sadako was the one who
- started them.
- What rumors?
The ones about assaulting the old
man and Yano being easy, right?
Yeah, I heard it was Sadako, too.
No way...
I will try my hardest and
will become their friend!
You're wrong! I know~
she would never do that!
Can you guys keep it
down? You're being too loud.
What's going on here?
Kuronuma is giving her all... -...to stop the
rumors about the two of you... to defend you
- both from the rumors. -Move!
- Outta the way!
- You're holding back, aren't you?
- Course I am!
But I can't interfere. I
have to stay out of it.
This is something they have to handle.
Just hang in there
Kuronuma. You've got this.
Don't give up.
Those words you said...
please take them back.
Huh? What the hell's
this? Don't touch me.
You're mistaken. Nothing you
said about them is true at all.
Are you guys hearing this right now?
I'm telling you, Yano and
Yoshida aren't what you say they are!
If they heard you say those things, I know
that it would really hurt their feelings.
Hey, don't stand here and act innocent!
You're one to talk about hurting nice
people's feelings, aren't you? -Every
single word about those two being a slut
and a delinquent, came directly from your
mouth. -From "me"?
Uh... W-Who?
Are you serious... I said all the rumors
circulating about Yano and Yoshida came
- from you!
- W-Wait... me?!
- Hey! Sadako got pushed!
- Maybe we should go break this up.
- Leave it to us.
I-I don't understand! Why would I ever say
anything bad about them? -I could never!
Because those two have always treated
me with nothing but absolute kindness, I
wouldn't-- -Shut up
already. I don't care about that.
We're just here to settle this with you
once and for all. Besides, if you want my
opinion...
I'm willing to bet they were only hanging
out with you for some kicks and giggles.
But they've probably gotten bored of
you. Clearly, you feel the same way.
Your reason for getting close to them was
to be around Kazehaya, wasn't it? At this
point, they're nothing but obstacles
for you, huh? You really piss me off.
You should stay away from everyone and
keep to yourself. -If you do that, then
maybe we'll actually think about
leaving you alo-- -You're wrong!
Huh?
You don't have to leave me alone.
Just... take back what you said.
What are you talking...
All of it... Everything
you're saying is wrong!
You don't get it. And how could you?
I guess it's 'cause... you
don't know anything about them.
-"It's because of how awesome you are"
- That win's completely yours.
While everyone else simply ignored me...
Here's a treat. So enjoy.
They never feared me or
pretended I didn't exist.
Dude, you're
drenched! Here's my track suit
Ew!
They've always treated me kindly,
even though they never had a reason to.
But you wouldn't know
any of that, would you?
You all have no idea how much I like both
Yano and Yoshida. More than I can put into
words.
Much more!
Sadako, do you like us?
I... I wouldn't exactly say "like"...
Instead of "like", I'd
say it's more, that--
I love them. That's why...
Y-Yoshida! She spread those rumors
about you and you're still gonna help her?
It wasn't Sadako.
- She'd never do something like that.
- What the hell are you--
- If we say it wasn't her,
then it wasn't and that's that.
Now get outta here
before I hafta force you out.
W- What gives?! Why don't you mind your
own business? I was talking to Sadako, not
to you guys!
Hmm? You've got some guts tryin' to order
me around like this. We went to the same
middle school so there's no
way you don't know, right?
About me winning 99 times in a row
against the guys I fought back then?
Seriously, Chizu?
You lay a finger on Sadako again
and I'll make sure you regret it.
- Fine! You can have that freak. Let's go!
- Please, wait! I want to make sure you
know that all the rumors you've heard are
false!
Ugh, you annoying
little... Yeah, okay, I get it!
I'll take back what I
said. Are you satisfied?
She actually... understood?
Hey, guys! Can you believe it?
I was able to get through to her!
There's no more misunderstanding!
Now they know... The rumors are false!
Sadako, It's all right.
Don't worry about it, okay?
It wasn't Sadako.
- She'd never do something like that.
Yano... Yoshida...
Thank you both...
...For believing in me. Thank you.
Uh, Kazehaya? Did we do
something... to make you mad?
- I am not mad!
- P-Please have mercy on us!
Look, it's just...
If there's one thing I
despise, it's gossip.
With that being said, everything about
Yano and Yoshida is a lie. You should know
better. Besides, you really think
Kuronuma would say those things?
Well- I y'know...
To be honest, I don't
actually know that much about her.
I guess since they were rumors, I
thought it was possible she could have
said it... So, yeah.
- No way. She fought hard to defend them.
- What do you mean?
Sadako was so brave. She kept trying to
protect their honor, even after she got
pushed down.
All we did was just stand and watch.
Eventually, Yano and Yoshida rushed
in to save Sadako from those bullies.
Whoa! She supposedly started all
this, but they still came to help her?
Yeah.
Then if that's the case, it means Sadako
wasn't really the one who was spreading
- the rumors after all.
- So that was rumor too!
I thought it sounded kind of sketchy.
Sadako's great. She
let me borrow her notes.
It was thanks to her that I was
able to ace my exams yesterday.
- Dude, same here!
- Sadako's pretty awesome, isn't she?
I knew it was just gossip. I
mean, it was totally obvious.
She'd be happy to
hear so many compliments.
And it's all thanks to Hirano and Endo
Nice job, you guys!
You did Sadako a solid!
You can do this, Kuronuma.
I guess I figured if I could clear
up a misunderstanding, I should.
Sadako...
For the longest time, I kept telling
myself that some things just can't be
helped. "If I failed again,
that's just how it goes."
While I always wanted to be closer with
everyone... Deep down, I... I must've given up
already.
But when it came to you, I
really didn't want that. Even if...
Even if I believe that being around you
could cause more rumors to spread, and
even worse... that I may upset or hurt you
both again... I can't do it... I can't bring
myself to give up on the two of you.
Please know, that if I do end up doing
something that hurts you again, when it
comes to comforting someone ~ I don't
really know how. Regardless, I'd still...
like to stick around
It'd be nice to stay with you guys exactly
like this. No... Actually, I want to become
even closer.
If there's a new problem... and it needs to
be straightened out, I'll do my best to
resolve it until everything's better.
I know I sound unreasonable and selfish.
Yet both of them have stood there the
entire time, and haven't looked away from
me even once. I can tell
they're really listening.
So I... would like to ask if
maybe you two would be my...
I would like it if we
could become friends!
Sadako, you thought... that Chizu and I
were upset because of those things... And
you assumed that by being around you
were doing nothing but causing us trouble.
You still wanted to be friends
with us but felt that you couldn't.
You poor thing... This is what you've
been dealing with all by yourself?
H-Hey, um... Be careful cause my
clothes are dirty from being on the floor...
Dummy!
You're so silly.
Jeez... I can't believe you already
answered every single question we were
gonna a--
I feel guilty for doubting you for even a
second, Sadako. I'm sorry! Really! Just
don't ever get used to being alone again.
Didn't you know? It's hard for us to do
anything but think the world of you. And
besides...
You're worried about friends... but you
don't realize, you already have them.
Sadako... You, me, and Yano... We are friends!
Wait, we are?
We already... are friends?
I can't hold back anymore! C'mere
and let me love on the two of you!
H-hey! You're gonna give everyone the
wrong idea! Are you trying to spread
another rumor?!
Jeez... you're a big
baby, you know that, Chizu?
- Friends, huh...
- Don't pretend you're not tearing up too!
I... I wanted...
Huh?
...To tell you that I
learned to tell a ghost story.
Wow... My very first real friends.
- Are they crying and laughing right now?
- Maybe it's some weird best friend thing.
- Should we call someone?
- Beats me...
They've reconciled!
With the main cast reunited,
harmony's been restored once more
Hey, y'hear that? Well, no need
for me to console Chizu, then.
Is there's a fight happening?! Where's it
going down? Who's fighting against who?
Outta the way, nerds!
What the?? What do you want? We're
kinda in the middle of something and
you're ruining it.
You three?! I was hoping for a
brawl, not a sappy little chick flick~
~...Alright~ somebody better
start throwing punches at someone!
You lunatic! You call
yourself a teacher?!
Aw crap! Move it! The Show's over!
I said scram, ya little rodents!
Make like a tree and get out of here!
Just like him to ruin the moment.
It's Kazehaya...
Congrats on pulling it off.
I heard your voice in my head
giving me words of encouragement.
"You can do it." "Don't give up."
You cheered me on the whole time.
Thank you... for everything.
- Did anyone else see that?
- Sadako was smiling.
No way. Didn't know that she could.
Soon after that, exams finally ended,
Unfortunately for me, I
didn't score very well.
Thirtieth? How'd you place that low?
- It's not as bad as you're making it seem.
- I was kinda dealing with
the lot the day exams started...
The average score of the rest of my
classmates rose dramatically for some
- reason...
- Yeah, me too!
- You saved our butts, Sadako!
Zashiki-warashi.
Sadako-warashi?!
It's possible I'm imagining it, but after
everything that happened, it seems like
everyone see me differently these days...
Even if it's only a little bit. Was I able
to do my best after all?
- Hey Sadako, let's go get some ramen.
- Oh! I-It's really okay if I tag along?
Of course! And you could even tell us
your ghost story while we're heading over.
Yeah! I can't wait for you to hear it!
Do we really have to?
- They only take cash, got any on you?
- A little, yeah.
You should be fine then.
Now that they're hanging out more,
there's no time for me to hang out with
- her.
- Hey, Kazahaya, wanna hang out today?
I haven't had ramen in a while!
You know what? I feel like
I've been completely reborn.
It all started, the day
that I met you, Kazehaya.
N- No fair...
You feeling okay?
Did you know? It's common for friends
to go get ramen together pretty often
I now have people in my life who are
very important to me. Whoa, is that true?
Don't let her fool you, she
just really likes her noodles.
With them by my side, I was able
to do things, I couldn't do alone.
After seeing that smile light up her face...
How could I ever dream of
getting in way of their friendship.
- Why are you on the floor?
- Do you need help getting up?
We can get the nurse if you need us to.
Hey! Sadako!
It's that girl.
Way to go! Looks like you achieved
your dream of making new friends.
Oh... Yes!
New friends...
Alright well, please be good to her!
Bye!
I've been validated!
- Sadako.
Huh?
- You said you didn't "like" us...
- Yeah, what was the
- other way you put it again?
- Uh... I...
- Go on...
I...
I love you two.
- Oh yeah? So, you love us, Sawako?
- Feeling's mutual!
After having met Kazehaya, so
much in my life has changed.
I've learned so many new feelings.
- Oh, right... How 'bout that ghost story?
- Yeah, tell it to us...
Okay! H-Hoichi was a fine lute player...
- You mean "Hoichi the Earless"?!
Oh man... Did you see
Kazehaya? He seemed pretty mad.
Yeah... He was talking about
how he hates stupid gossip.
I think he
specifically meant us, didn't he?
- Do you think she's gonna be okay?
- Why?
It's just that Yuka's had a huge crush
on Kazehaya ever since middle school.
Hey!
- Wait!
- Yuka!
Such stupid girls.
I don't know what they expected. When
you make a big scene like that, of course
Kazehaya is gonna hate you.
All of the friends that I love.
A priceless moment.
Next time: "Saturday Night"